Things to buy:
- Mesh for microphone
- skin care product research
- Drink 3 liters



<!DOCTYPE html> <!-- start -->
<html lang="en"> 
<head>  <!-- metadata inserted for text rendering, width, zoom -->
    <meta charset="UTF-8">
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0">
    <title>Construction Website</title>
</head>
<body style="color: rgb(33, 24, 24);">
    <h1 style="color: blue;
    font-family: 'Times New Roman', Times, serif;
    font-size: 60px;">This is Alfredo's Maintenance company Website</h1> <!-- Header -->
    <p>This is a paragraph that will change your life. Now.. I'm sure that this has never been uttered before, so blessed be your ears ("sarcasm")..</p>
    <textarea placeholder= "Kindly provide your email"></textarea>

    <br>

    <button style="background-color: blue;
    color: aliceblue;
    border: none;
    padding: 20px;
    margin: 20px" type="button">Click Me!</button>

    <img src="AMC Header.png" alt = "Image" height="230px" />
</body>
</html>



   <p>Alfredo's Maintenance Company has long been a trusted name in the Lake Tahoe area, established by a founder whose commitment to creativity, hard work, and trust set the standard for quality.

        
        Now, as leadership passes to a motivated and experienced son, the company embraces a fresh vision that builds on its storied past.

        
        
        Our talented team of professionals continues to deliver the highest quality craftsmanship available, combining hands-on expertise with modern design sensibilities. Known throughout the area for our distinctive ability to tailor projects uniquely to each client's vision, we engage you directly in the creative process. This collaborative approach ensures that every detail is thoughtfully addressed, resulting in final products that are as unique as they are timeless.
        
        
        
        As a hands-on builder—not just another contractor—I bring a wealth of experience to every project alongside a committed team of experts. Our streamlined process emphasizes efficiency, clear communication, and budget-conscious planning, ensuring that projects move swiftly without unnecessary bureaucratic delays.
        

        At Alfredo's Maintenance Company, quality craftsmanship and personalized service remain our hallmarks. With a renewed passion for excellence, we continue to transform ideas into lasting works of art that stand the test of time.</p> <!-- Header -->
        

 <!-- I don't know I just don't believe that girls find captivating
  --> They don't say thirsty comments to me

    -->They talk about how attractive other guys are

      --> Girls don't pursue me.

      <img src="flooring2.jpg" alt="Flooring" style="width:100%">

        
     <img src="Snow.jpeg" alt="Flooring" style="width:100%">
        

        <body style="background-color:(219, 213, 213)">
<a class="center-text" href="tel:530-523-3643">530-523-3643</a>
        Phone: <span itemprop="telephone"><a href="tel:530-523-3643">
        530-523-3643</a></span>
    
          <a class="center-text" href="tel:209-327-7987">209-327-7987</a>
 <textarea class="center-text-three"  placeholder= "Kindly provide your email"></textarea>



    <br>

    <p class="center-line">
        Please procide your Name:
    <div class="formfield">
        <label for="textarea">Label for textarea</label>

        <textarea id="textarea" rows="5">Textarea</textarea>
      </div>

      button.left {
    left: 30%; /* Position the first button far left */
    
  }
  
  button.middle {
    text-align: center;
    left: 45%; /* Position the second button in the middle */
  }
  button.right {
    left: 63%; /* Position the second button in the middle */
  }
